#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/liz-montelibano-62965979 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Hospitals

Nursing

**Patient Safety** 

### Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

**PALS** 

Certified Nurse Operative Room (CNOR)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

# Liz Montelibano

RN, BSN, CNOR

San Francisco Bay Area

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Hospitals, Basic Life Support (BLS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science Nursing, RN license in California, CNOR with over 20 years experience in Surgery department

## Experience

Santa Clara County / OConnor Hospital Clinical Nurse III/ Operating Room March 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) San Jose, California

O'Connor Hospital BSN ,RN, CNOR July 2001 - Present (18 years 11 months)

Kaiser Permanente
OR RN
April 2007 - November 2007 (8 months)

Seton Medical Center
OR RN
October 1996 - April 1998 (1 year 7 months)

HRN Services
Travel RN
January 1996 - October 1997 (1 year 10 months)

Palo Alto VA Hospital RN July 1996 - October 1996 (4 months) Palo Alto, California OR RN

US Army
Operating Room Specialist
October 1992 - December 1995 (3 years 3 months)

## Education

Velez College

Bachelor of Science Nursing, CNOR, /Registered Nurse/Surgery department

Velez College